<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--
   New Perspectives on XML 3rd Edition
   Tutorial 6
   Tutorial Case
   Terrence Chan
   3/4/2021
   Harpe Gaming Store Products

   Filename:         products.xml
   Supporting Files: products.xsl

-->
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="products.xsl" ?>
<products>
    <product pid="vg10551">
        <title>Dance Off VII</title>
        <manufacturer>Anasta Games</manufacturer>
        <price>29.95</price>
        <releaseDate>2017-09-28</releaseDate>
        <media>Video Game</media>
        <image>vg10551.png</image>
        <summary>
            <h3>Challenge Yourself with Dance</h3>
            <p>
                <i>Dance Off VII</i> is the highly-anticipated sequel in the
                <i>Dance Off</i> line of dance games, brings even more fun and
         challenges to your gaming console. Take advantage of your motion-control
         platform and 50 of the hottest dance tracks to challenge
         the world - or your best friends - to
                <i>Dance Off</i>.
            </p>
            <p>You wanted the top stars and hit songs and we got 'em for this new release.
         But don't think we dropped your old favorites and standards. Every
         track from
                <i>Dance Off III</i> is available and fully compatible with
         the new release. An added bonus: downloadable tracks from the top
         songs on the charts, so you can dance off to current hits.
            </p>
            <p>
                <i>Dance Off VII</i> is the ultimate party game. The challenges are
         endless. Let the boys challenge the girls or the kids challenge the
         parents. Go international and stage your own Dance Off Olympics against
         friends from around the world. Dancers can track their standings on
         global leader boards and follow stats from dancers around the world.
            </p>
        </summary>
    </product>
    <product pid="vg10552">
        <title>Net Force 12</title>
        <manufacturer>Nitta Sports</manufacturer>
        <price>35.72</price>
        <releaseDate>2017-10-03</releaseDate>
        <media>Video Game</media>
        <image>vg10552.png</image>
        <summary>
            <h3>Take the Battle to the Hardwood</h3>
            <p>
                <i>Net Force 12</i> is the latest release in the Net Force series of basketball
         simulation games. Using motion capture technology designed specifically for
                <i>Net Force</i>, this release captures the signature moves of the top players in
         the NBA, . No other basketball simulation has this lineup of stars. Additional
         features include support for motion-sensor game controllers, dynamic shot
         generation, touch-sensitive passing, and "flash-to-the-hoop" acceleration
         for uncontested slam dunks.
            </p>
            <p>Go to basketball camp and learn the game the right way with a series of fun
         and challenging tutorials. Relive the past with stars from the 60's, 70's, 80's,
         and 90's. Can today's stars hold their own against the champs from the past?
         You decide.</p>
            <p>Take your virtual game to a new entertainment level with the dynamic background
         music and production by some of the top hip-hop artists on the charts. Previous
         releases of
                <i>Net Force</i> have already won multiple awards for music and
         production and this release looks posed to continue that winning streak.
            </p>
        </summary>
    </product>
</products>