<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--
   New Perspectives on XML 3rd Edition
   Tutorial 6
   Tutorial Case
   Terrence Chan
   3/4/2021
   Harpe Gaming Store Product Reviews

   Filename:         reviews.xml
   Supporting Files:

-->

<r:reviews
 xmlns:r="http://example.com/reviews">

   <r:review cid="22088" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-18</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Another Great Edition in a Great Series</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I'm a big fan of this product. As great as Version 11 was, I think this version is
         more realistic and responsive. It's not perfect. I found the controller system still 
         a bit too complicated. Muscle memory helps a bit, but it could still use some 
         improvement.
         </p>
         <p>But that's a minor complaint. Compared to other games on the market, this is a great game
         at a great price.
         </p>
         <p>The music I can take or leave. I know that some players really get into the sound track. To
         me it's a lot of noise and very repetitive. I recommend picking this game up, even if you own 
         Version 11. It's a substantial upgrade and well worth the price.
         </p>
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="57124" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-18</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>My Favorite Workout Video and Workout Game</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I've owned all of the Dance Off releases from the beginning. It's my favorite workout
         video every morning. I have lost 12 pounds with very little modification of my diet.
         </p>
         <p>Dance Off just gets better with every release. The song tracks are great. There is a wonderful
         selection of new and old tracks from around the world; some obscure and others more popular, 
         including several that are in heavy rotation on the radio right now. Most tracks have several
         choreographic alternatives that can be unlocked by earning in-game dance points.
         </p>
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="34811" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>3</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-17</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Poor Choreography</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>A so-so release of this well-established title. The user interface is improved and easier to use and
         game provides a few great songs, a few terrible ones, and several mediocre ones. The graphics are 
         beautiful and the sets are stunning and fun (without being distracting.)
         </p>
         <p>Where this release fails is in the choreography. The dances just aren't as much fun as the previous 
         titles. Many of the moves follow predictable patterns; they're stale and that's a big problem for a 
         dance game. I hope the next release improves the choreography because it's great in all other
         phases of the game.
         </p>
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="41403" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-17</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>A Great Gift</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I bought this for my 13 year old daughter and her friends. They had exhausted the songs from the
         earlier releases and looking for a new challenge. This release includes the most current songs with
         GREAT new moves. My daughter also likes the new format and is getting hours of fun (and exercise!) 
         out of the game. 
         </p>
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="31115" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>3</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-17</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Great Offense Poor Defense - Just Like the Pro's</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>The game is great when I have the ball and can drive to the rim or dish for the quick 3; but I hate 
         playing defense. The controls are difficult and unintuitive. Where's the fun when you go in for a jam and
         then see your opponent do the same to you because your feet are stuck in cement?
         </p>
         <p>And don't suggest that I go to Basketball Camp. That stuff sounds good but the tips and lessons don't
         translate well to game conditions.
         </p>
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="21884" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-17</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>A Very Nice Upgrade with Things to Attract All Ages</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>If you've played any of the previous Dance Off release then you know what to expect from this fun
         game. New users: give it a try.  It's kind of goofy and a lot of fun and unlike other games, it's a
         great source of exercise for "couch potatoes. It's not just for kids; sneak in some exercise when your
         children are away.
         </p>
         <p>This new release works the same way as the previous entries in this series: select a song and follow the 
         animated dancers on the monitor; closely mimic their moves and gain points, fall off the routine and lose
         points. The songs focus on the current pop stars, but there are a few classic pop and rock standards from 
         the 70's, 60's, and 50's.
         </p>
         <p>Be sure to explore the World Dance mode where you can play with friends online.
         </p>
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="38609" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>1</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-16</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Buggy with Poor Tech Support</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>The installation was buggy and kept crashing my gaming console. I spent several hours on tech support
         with no solution to my problem. I finally returned it and got my money back. I wish I could give it a
         zero star rating. FIX IT ANASTA!!!!
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="37890" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>4</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-17</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Almost as Good as the Real Thing</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I've been waiting for this release. It's a great game and you won't be able to stop playing. I would 
         recommend this game to the basketball fans, but really anyone can enjoy this one.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="31004" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-16</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Great Fun and Variety</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I popped this into my gaming console and was up and dancing in just a few minutes. I did have a few minor
         problems downloading some of the new music tracks but the company sent me a patch and the issue was
         quickly resolved.
         </p>
         <p><i>Dance Off</i> provides a great variety of songs spanning different genres and a lot of good upbeat pop music. 
         The group dances are fun too where you and your friends can enjoy goofy and fun choreography. The backgrounds and 
         costumes have gotten quite elaborate in this new release. I especially enjoyed the Disney-themed stage with characters
         from several of the Princess movies.
         </p>
         <p>A nice bonus is you can also hook up a usb microphone to get karaoke points. This release has it all!!!
         </p>     
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="35693" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>1</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-16</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Stopped Working Soon after Purchase</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I was so looking forward to this release. I got about 10 games out of it and then my gaming console stopped reading
         the disk. The disk is clean and free of scratches. All of the other games are still working just fine.
         </p>     
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="45983" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-16</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Keeps Getting Better</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I've enjoyed this game from Version 1.0 and this release did not let me down. World Dance is a great new feature that 
         lets you feel connected to dancers across the world. The have a good mix of old and new songs. The ability to setup a 
         custom playlist is another feature I love about this game. 
         </p>
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="26727" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>3</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-16</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Inappropriate for Some Ages</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>It's a nice game with some clever graphics; but I found this release with several sound tracks of questionable taste and
         content to be poorly suited to my younger nieces. The rating should not have been 10+ years of age. It should be older. 
         They should have provided an age-filter for those of us who care about what our kids are listening to.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="26991" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>2</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-16</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Too Many Changes, Too Few Improvements</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>It's fun but frustrating because you have to basically relearn all the controls and button combinations all over again. 
         Why did they have to change everything? The enhancements are only okay at best and distracting at worst. My son hates
         this release and just goes back to Version 11. Save your money and wait for Version 13 (which might be a lucky number
         for a change.)
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="39541" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-16</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>A Great Game and a Great Workout. I Loved the Variety</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I've been buying Dance Off since it first came out and I'm really happy with this upgrade. The choreography is difficult 
         but keep dancing! You'll quickly get the hang of it and then the fun really starts. I sometimes use this game 
         in place of my morning exercise class. You won't work up a sweat at first because you'll be learning the steps. Once
         you have the routines mastered, you'll be burning off more calories than in the toughest aerobic workouts.
         </p>
         <p>The variety is GREAT! It doesn't include only American pop hits. I love the Latin music stage. I also like the fact
         that once you learn the dance for the song, you can download other dances for the same song.   </p>
         <p>I don't like that I'm the only one playing this game at my home, so the World Dance feature is a great bonus. I don't really
         care about the points system and getting on the "leader board." That's not why I play this game; but if that's your 
         motivation, then go for it. 
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="21477" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>3</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-15</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Not Responsive Enough</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>This is my first experience with Dance Off. I've danced all of my life, so playing a video game version of dancing 
         has not interested me. I decided however to give it a try after hearing from my friends how great this game was.
         </p>
         <p>The choreography is difficult, but an average dancer will pick it up. I was able follow the steps and get some of the
         routines mastered. Sometimes however the game doesn't count my moves properly. I had to exaggerate my moves in order
         to get recognized. I'm petite but that shouldn't make difference.
         </p>
         <p>I'll keep this game because I like the exercise aspect of it; but the point system doesn't really work. My advice
         is to ignore the point counter because it really doesn't work well and you can have enough fun doing the routines.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="19133" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-15</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>This Game Changed My Life; It WILL Change Yours</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>Gather Round and Listen to Me Children, <br />
         This is the game you've been waiting for.<br />
         Let it lead you to the Promised Land<br />
         Of Thunderous Dunks and No Look Passes<br />
         Ignore your Classes<br />
         Forget your Friends<br />
         They are now your Enemies!<br />
         The Ball is All<br />
         <br />
         --- The Whipper
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="19815" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-15</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>A hard hard hard Game but well worth the time</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>The new release of <i>Dance Off</i> is finally here. There are many new and exciting features and the soundtrack shows a
         great variety of tunes and styles. I was pleasantly surprised by the 80's music stage.
         </p>
         <p>There are some flaws with this release. They switched the  format (why???) and you relearn all of your old 
         moves. Still, it's beautiful and worth the money I like earning points while dancing and I like cashing in 
         those points to reveal hidden features and stages. The calorie burning data is awesome. That feature is
         great for those of you who use this game for exercise.   </p>
         <p>Look for me on the Leader Board, burning up the stage. Ha! 
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="48881" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>3</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-15</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Improve the Choreography PLEASE</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>This is the fifth <i>Dance Off</i> title that I own. The user interface is the best so far and is easy to use. 
         The music selection is on par with other dance games: a few great songs but some which are best described
         as "filler." Some games are not improved by adding "more" and this is one of them. I like the graphics and
         the variety of stages.
         </p>
         <p>Still, this only gets 3 stars from me because of the choreography. The dances just aren't as much fun as 
         they were in previous releases. I think the moves are predictable and repetitive. More variation would have
         been better. It's a shame because the developers did so much right in other areas of the game.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="43512" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-15</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Loved It</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I bought this as a birthday present for my granddaughter. She absolutely loves it.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="42001" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>1</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-15</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Lots of Problems</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>The passing feature on this game is a total waste. The game is sluggish and difficult 
         to use. You're better off just tossing the ball up in the air and hoping it lands in a teammate's
         hands. Dribbling is even worse. 
         </p>
         <p>Everyone hates refs in a real basketball game, so why do they make the refs an ever-present part of
         this game? Sure, let's play a game and listen to the refs blow their whistles for the next 10 minutes.
         Free throws!!! Yeah, that's what we want to do in a basketball simulation!!
         </p>
         <p>The only positive thing is the music. Save your money and download the MP3 tracks if that's what turns
         you on.
         </p>
         <p>Dunking is fun, I'll give you that. And I did enjoy pitting the stars of yesteryear against the stars 
         of today. But this needs some really improvement in Version 13 or I'm outta here. 
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="28760" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>4</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-15</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Pretty Good but Limited Use</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>It's a dance game and one of the best games on the market; however, I found that after a week I had
         pretty much mastered all of the routines. I'll probably load this one from time to time but not 
         more than that.
         </p>
         <p>If you like dance games, then this is a good one to get.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="50128" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-15</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>I Love the New World Dance!!</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I just picked this one up and I think it's fantastic!!! Fun songs, great moves! Hours, literally hours
         of fun with your friends.   </p>
         <p>What really puts this release over the top is the <b>World Dance stage</b>. I love playing against other dancers
         across the globe and I've made some new friends that way. It doesn't hurt to see my name on the leader
         boards either. This feature helped me break out of rut and try new songs and moves.
         </p>
         <p>My only complaint is that there are a few songs in which the movement skips. I don't know whether to blame our
         gaming console or the game itself. I did not notice this problem on earlier releases. Perhaps I need to upgrade
         my system because the motion control features do require a lot of processing power.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="42188" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>4</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-14</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Just Okay</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I'm not a big dance game fan (first person shooters are more my interest.) So if you like this kind of game,
         you'll probably like this release a lot. I think the different dance stages add variety and interest
         to the game. The music is okay for the most part (the type of music I like wouldn't really work for
         a dance game.)
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="30144" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>4</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-14</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Great Gift</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I bought this game for my daughter for her birthday. She absolutely LOVES it. The learning curve was a little
         steep but once she mastered the game play, there was no stopping her.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="33873" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>4</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-13</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Another Nice Release</r:title>
      <r:description>
        <p>Another nice release in a venerable and classic title. The graphics are greatly improved for this release and
        the updated playlist is nice. I like the World Dance stage though I probably won't use it too much. I'm more
        of a soloist myself. I like to dance but I don't like to compete.   </p>
        <p>The software could be a bit more responsive however. I found myself making moves that did not register on the
        screen. And then I began overcompensating for this glitch and that made me feel that I was doing less dancing
        and more stomping. The movement should be seamless and it's not. However it's still better than any other
        dance game out there.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="37714" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>4</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-13</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Great Game Play, Great Music, Need More Time!</r:title>
      <r:description>
        <p>The graphics were amazing and the sound track blew me away. This is a really nice edition of a long-established
        classic. I especially loved the franchise play and creating my own team of stars from the past and present.
        I've read about how other people have had trouble playing the game. Have these people every played
        a sports simulation before? You have to put time into it if you want success.
        </p>
        <p>Now, what I didn't like: The timer seemed off. I barely had time to set up my offense when I ran out of time.
        I've gotten better, but they need to give players the options to extend the timing on the shot clock --- or
        remove it completely.
        </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="21921" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-12</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Release the Dancer Inside</r:title>
      <r:description>
        <p>Just a fantastic game. It's already given me hours and hours of pleasure. EXTREMELY WELL-DONE!!!
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="28442" pid="vg10551">
      <r:rating>5</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-12</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Great for International Parties</r:title>
      <r:description>
        <p>I'm an exchange student here in the United States. I can't tell you how much I enjoyed the World Stage
        feature of this game. It allows me to reconnect with my friends back home, who I greatly miss! Now,
        on a Saturday night we can party and the miles don't seem quite as long.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="20014" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>1</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-12</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>A Big Disappointment</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I was really looking forward to this release, but I didn't see anything new and worth my money. It looks
        like they took the old game, adding a few bells and whistles (and annoying music) but didn't really improve
        the game play any.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="22783" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>2</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-12</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>This Title has Been Passed By</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p><i>Net Force</i> used to be the standard in basketball simulation games. However several titles released in
         the last year have raised the bar. This version looks like the company is standing still and resting on
         their laurels. I'll wait until Version 13 thanks.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="31552" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>1</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-11</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Not Worth the Time or the Effort</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>I got this gift for my birthday. I'm not much of a sports simulation fan, so I returned it after a few games.
         I don't understand the attraction.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="27042" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>4</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-10</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Still the Best Basketball Game Around</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>The competition is getting fierce, but <i>Net Force</i> is still a force to be reckoned with in
         sports simulation industry. I would have wished for a little more innovation in this release (the
         controller system HAS to be improved.)
         </p>
         <p>That being said, no other game provides a better simulation of a real game. And adding the stars
         of previous decades is a great feature. I even enjoyed the basketball camp.   </p>
         <p>People who complain about this title are just haters. And haters gotta hate.
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
   <r:review cid="26714" pid="vg10552">
      <r:rating>1</r:rating>
      <r:reviewDate>2017-11-09</r:reviewDate>
      <r:title>Where's the Quality Control??</r:title>
      <r:description>
         <p>The software crashed and crashed again. Tech support gave me the run-around (after spending 2
         hours trouble-shooting the problem.   </p>
         <p>Why bother selling a product if you're not going to stand by it and HELP the customer?
         Where's the quality control?
         </p>      
      </r:description>
   </r:review>
</r:reviews>